Dear WWS channel viewers, my name is Hinata Hashigami.
Yes, I am a bit nervous now that I am on my own,
I have a lot of things I have to do on my own,
I am looking forward to it the most. I am looking forward to it.
Well, it took about six months from the time I graduated from EBICHU to my debut.
So I had to take some time off while preparing for my debut.
Of course, I was in a group, but the reason I joined the agency was because I wanted to become someone who could sing and dance by myself,
I wanted to pursue that dream again, so I decided to try my hand at solo singing again, and this time I went solo.
I had a chance to sing in the past, but I had been in a group for so long that I knew all the fun of being in a group, and I thought it would be better this way,
But as I grew older and started to play more and more music, I wanted to challenge myself more and more,
I thought I would like to pursue this dream again, so I decided to try my hand at a solo career.
It was my birthday when I announced that I was going to make my debut.
When I announced the title of the song the other day, I received comments from the members saying they were looking forward to it, so everyone gave me a push and I left the group. I had to leave the group, but still, I felt like everyone was
I am very happy to know that everyone is still as happy and looking forward to it as I am.
The environment was different from when I was in EBICHU, so I learned a lot there, and I also learned a lot of new things.
I also wanted to change, or rather, I wanted to change more and more.
I wanted to change, or rather, I wanted to change rapidly, and I wanted to change my songs, the way I sing, and the things I do.
Yes, from head to toe.
From bow to toe is the meaning of the phrase,
I want to deliver this music to you with my whole body,
I hope that everyone will be exposed to this music with their whole body,
The music itself is powerful and gorgeous,
The music itself is powerful and glamorous, a bit like a musical or a show.
There is a lot of shouting and such.
I don't know when we are going to do the live performance, but I hope everyone will remember it for when we do it.
There is no overlap at all this time. I've done a lot of music and various genres when I was a member of a group, but this time, I don't think I'll be doing the same thing again.
I thought it would be good for me not to be in the same group again, so I participated in the process of choosing the music this time.
I wanted to keep what we have done so far, but I also wanted to encounter more and more things that I had not encountered before, so this time, I decided to make a new album.
undefined